RIVAN NURDIN

Backend Developer

An ordinary human who happened to be destined to become a Backend Developer in 2017 until now. 5+ years of experience building Management APIs. I enjoy working on lean and agile development projects using Scrum. I'm equally working as a part of team to come up with a creative thoughts and also capable of working independently.

□ rivannurdin001@gmail.com

(2) +62 813-8723-6169

github.com/rivan-codes

Relevant Experience

Freelance Backend Developer

Aug 2021 - Now

- Handling multiple backend projects from clients.
- Plan and implement the required technology architecture.
- Reporting the results of work in the form of API documentation

Backend Developer @ Hexa Maju Samasta

Nov 2019 - Jul 2021 // Bandung, ID

- Wrote and defined clean codes to achieve functional and sustainable web applications.
- Assessed data to recommend and plan installation of new systems or modifications of existing ones.
- Enhanced working relationships by participating in teambuilding activities.

Backend Developer @ Exaditama Teknologi Kreativa

May - Oct 2019 // Bandung, ID

Focuses on the database, scripting, and architecture of an API program, with designs that have been created by the project manager.

Junior Web Developer @ Exa Aditama Internasional

Jun 2017 - Dec 2018 // Bandung, ID

Responsible for building the base code, working closely with senior developers, and streamlining the entire development process.

Education

ARS University

2019 - 2023 (Expected) Informatics Engineering

Vocational High School Pelita Bandung

2015-2017

Computer Software Engineering

Skills

Backend Framework

PHP (Laravel, Codelgniter, Phalcon), Python (Fastapi, Django), .NET, NodeJS (Expressjs), .NET Core

Frontend Framework

JQuery, Bootstrap, ReactJS

Database

MySQL, PostgreSQL, SQL Server

Tools & Platforms

GIT, Apache, REST APIs, Postman, S3 Storage, Firebase, Swagger, Wordpress, Azure

Projects

Djangkep Apps

Application for submitting a certificate in the related Village In Bali

UseeTV

Web-based application for managing customer data at Indihome

MoBooking

Online service booking to meet all daily needs

KMOB Platform

Application Presence, Performance and Mobile Services for Governments

MY TREATS ASIA

marketplace that provides a collection of offers and e-vouchers from local

Onderdil Cepat

marketplace that provides motorcycle and car spare parts

FASTPUM

Application for submitting licenses, appointments and dismissal of regional

SIMELON

Web based application in Pertamina for reporting Gas LPG 3 kg

Service Desk Telkom University

Web-based application for students, lecturers, employees in making suggestion and complaint tickets